Okay, great.
Hi, my name is Sylvia Russell, and today, we're going to give you some tips on how to make home remedies for under-eye circles and puffiness.
Now, the first thing you want to remember is you want to always be careful about what you use on your eye area.
The eye area is very sensitive, so we don't want to use anything that's going to damage or irritate the eye.
One tip for under-eye circles or puffiness is to use a cold compress. Take a washcloth, wet it down with some water, and put it in your freezer for a few minutes.
Then, once it's done lay it on your eyes for five to ten minutes, giving yourself a little mini eye mask.
This is a great way to take any puffiness that has accumulated around the eye. Another great way to reduce eye puffiness is to cut some cucumbers that have been in the refrigerator and place these on the eye.
These are a great way to reduce eye puffiness, but it also looks very spa-like. Another remedy is to make sure that you analyze the eye very well, and figure out the reason why you may be puffy, or why you may have under-eye circles.
Did you stay up late last night? Did you have fun at a party? These are all ways to have, to wake up with a puffy eye.
So remember, if you have eye puffiness make sure and use cold compresses, cucumbers; great things that you can find at home.
My name is Sylvia Russell, and this is how you can use home remedies to get rid of eye puffiness and under eye circles.